(a): it could make editing a file easier because you can see on what version the problems in a code started
(b): whenever a large enough change is made, if you make small changes that don't do much, they don't need to be saved but a big change should be saved because it takes more work to do and losing it would be bad
(c): it tells the other members which files to check over if something is wrong and lets them know if its code they want